I am welcome to Jim of detail I'm Johnny
today I'll be doing a review video on
the tattoo product real skin now this
video isn't sponsored by real skin and I
haven't been asked to do this video by
real skin but this video is my own
personal honest opinion on how good the
product is how much better it is
compared to the cheap ones you can buy
online and why you should be using this
to practice your tattoo and on compared
to the cheaper products as well so just
to start off with I'm gonna be showing
you how much more realistic it is
compared to the cheaper products as you
can see straight away on here the real
skin is obviously more realistic in
color compared to the cheaper stuff if
you pinch the real the real skin as well
it's also pinches more like obviously
the real thing and this way this one
doesn't at all it's like a lever and it
hardly moves at all if you look at the
thickness of the real skin as well and
how much more stretches like real skin
is so much more authentic if I just show
you the cheaper stuff here you can see
how much more thinner it is and it
hardly stretches at all it's more like
as that is more like lever so I'll be
showing you on here how much more easier
it is to tattoo one so I've got a shader
here with a 50 mark setup on it so what
I'll do now I'll show you how much
easier it is to sort of shade on and how
much more realistic it is to shade on
compared to the cheaper stuff so if I
just get some ink picked up here
right so I'll shade now on the cheaper
product to show you show you the
difference
[Music]
[Laughter]
my straightaway there I just doing a
flat sheet across you can see the lines
that appears on the fake skin it's not
very realistic at all so I wanna do
we're gonna do standard Shadia
[Laughter]
what I find with this product is it
rejects the ink and it also because it's
so is soul every like pushes the needle
out so you don't get a very realistic
tattoo experience with it at all it's
it's okay I sort of to practice on but I
I just I don't know I don't like the
feel of it at all is it's terrible
compared to this product as you can see
again by they're just showing you that
it's not very realistic shade on it at
all so let me show you now how much more
better this product is and why you
should be using this to practice your
tattoo and on
[Music]
so you could hear straight away there
how much better that was and if you look
if you look close the idea how much more
realistic the shade is on there and
again I'm gonna just do a standard shade
here again
[Music]
now this feels so much better to talk to
one the thickness of it compared you'll
see is more authentic to real skin but
the feel of it is so much better as well
if we just wipe bad off a second
obviously this I find this wipes off
much better on this product as well like
real skin does but if you look at that
the shade on it is just so much more
realistic compared to what it would be
like if you were tattooing on real skin
it's such a nicer product to use and the
feel of it is so much nicer said if I do
it again on here just so you can hear
the difference I mean you can feel it
you can hear that straight away it's
like it's trying to push the needle out
is it
it grips it also grips the needle as
well it's like it's trying to fight
against me trying to tattoo on into it
is the the feel of it is really bad it's
actually pushing the needle back up into
the machine where so if we tattoo on
here
now that is exactly what it should be
like such such a better product I mean
as I said you should obviously
definitely try it yourself
it's well worth the money is
it's a very very realistic product
obviously this is the product that I'll
be using for now on I won't be waste any
more money on products like this this is
a lot easier to learn your TAS going on
also the good thing with this it's good
to be able to learn needle depth Lee
obviously needle control obviously
trying to get more used to have the feel
it should be when you're actually
tattooing on real skin and obviously
getting used to the obviously the depth
you should be tattooing on but so this
is a much better product well worth the
money and if you are going to be
purchasing any products to actually
learn tattoo it on this would be the
best one to go on to now their actual
website is www.antakungfu.com there if
you if you want to purchase a really
good product to learn on this is the
best one so as I said I'll see you all
soon
and please if you are going to learn
this would be the one to learn on thank
you and throw up